Local 1199 Additional Records 5651
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Local 1199 Additional Records
1942-1979
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU)
RWDSU Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Employees Union
5651
64 cubic feet
64 linear ft.
Records (documents), minutes (administrative records), correspondence, collective labor agreements.
Correspondence, membership records, meeting reports, memorandums and meeting minutes
3121898
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 18, 2005
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 25, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5651: Local 1199 Additional Records 5510: Local 1199 Records 5871: Local 1199 Additional Records 6281m: Local 1199 Biography files 5206-S: Local 1199 Executive Secretary Moe Foner Records 5206-X: Local 1199 Clippings and News Releases 5206-D: Local 1199 Drug Division Records 5206-G: Local 1199 Guild Division Records 5206-PR: Local 1199 President Leon Davis Records 6206: Clyde Summers Office Files 5948: Local 1199 (Rochester, N.Y.) Records 5680 OH: Local 1199 Oral History Project
Health facilities--Employees--Labor unions--New York (State)--New York--Sources.; Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union; Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union. Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Employees Union (New York, N.Y.)
3121898
- Arbitration, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Contributions, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, Contributions, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, Foreign, 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, Membership, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, Membership, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, Union, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Court Cases, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Credit Unions, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Davis, Personal, 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Davis, Speeches & Invitations, 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- District 1199, Baltimore, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- District 1199, Connecticut, 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- District 1199, Massachusetts, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- District 1199, Philadelphia, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- District 1199, Washington, DC, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- District 1199E- Baltimore, 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- District 1199J, New Jersey, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- District 1199P, Pennsylvania, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Division Activity Reports, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Executive Board Meeting, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Executive Council Reports, 1975-1978 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Executive Council Reports, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Health and Hospital Corp., 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Hearings and Appeals Board, 1975-1978 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Hospitals, 1975-1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Housing 1199-Plaza, 1974-1978 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Housing Corporation, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Incentive Systems, 1975-1978 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Lay-offs (Box 7, Folder 2)
- League of Voluntary Hospitals and Homes, 1973-1978 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Local 1199 Massachusetts, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Local 1199 West Virginia, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Local 1199C Philadelphia, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Local 1199D Durham, NC, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Local 1199P Philadelphia, PA, 1972-1975 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Membership Letters, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Memorandums, 1973-1978 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- National Benefit Fund, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- National Benefit Plan, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- N.R.L.A., 1975-1978 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- National Union Convention, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- National Union Executive Board Meeting, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- National Union Executive Board Meeting, 1976-1978 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Negotiations, 1974-1978 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Negotiations, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Negotiations, Federal Mediation & Conciliation, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Negotiations, League and Hospital Correspondence, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Negotiations, Meeting Notices and Minutes, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Negotiations, Negotiating Comm. and SubComm., 1976 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Negotiations, Publicity Campaign, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Negotiations, Reports and Proposals, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- New Jersey, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- NY Central Labor Council, 1975-1978 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- News, 1973-1978 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Nursing Homes, 1975-1978 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Office of Collective Bargaining, 1975-1977 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Plaza Housing Corp., 1975-1978 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Proposals-Researched Information, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- R.N. Campaign, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Reports on District 1199, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Reports on District 1199, 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Requests for Employment (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Retirees, 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Securely Guards (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Sipster & Weinstock, 1975-1978 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Staff, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Staff, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Training and Upgrading Fund, 1975-1977 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Training and Upgrading Fund, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Monthly Division Activities Reports, 1975-1978 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Monthly Statistical Reports, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Monthly Statistical Reports, 1975-1978 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Chapter Meeting Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Delegate Assembly - Cornell, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Executive Board Meeting, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Executive Board Minutes, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Labor-Management Services - Administration EP. Reports, 1959-1963 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- National Board Meetings and Conferences (Box 17, Folder 6)
- National Union Conference, 1971-1973 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- National Union Convention, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- National Union Convention, Officers Reports, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- National Union Founding Conference, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- National Union Monthly Reports, 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Soviet Union, 1972-1975 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Spain-Portugal, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Alabama, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Arkansas, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- By-Laws, 1973-1975 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- By-Laws, District 1199 Massachusetts, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- By-Laws, District 1199C Philadelphia, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- California, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Colorado, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Connecticut, 1972-1975 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Delaware, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Federationist (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Florida, 1972-1975 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Georgia, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Hawaii, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Illinois, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Indiana, 1972-1975 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Iowa, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Kansas, 1971-1975 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Kentucky, 1972-1975 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Louisiana, 1972-1975 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Maine, 1972-1975 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Maryland, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Massachusetts, 1972-1975 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Michigan, 1973-1975 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Minnesota, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Mississippi, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Missouri, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Missouri-Kansas City-Government Wages, 1973-1975 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Montana, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Nebraska, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Nebraska-Omaha, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Nevada, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- New Hampshire, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 32)
- New Jersey, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- New Jersey-Newark, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 34)
- New Mexico, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 35)
- New York, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 36)
- New York-Rochester, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 37)
- North Carolina, 1972-1974 (Box 19, Folder 38)
- North Dakota, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 39)
- Ohio, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 40)
- Ohio-Cleveland, 1972-1975 (Box 19, Folder 41)
- Oregon, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 42)
- Pennsylvania, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 43)
- Pennsylvania Labor Market Letter Philadelphia, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 44)
- Pennsylvania Labor Relations Board (Box 19, Folder 45)
- Pennsylvania-Philadelphia Employment (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Religious Hospitals, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Residents and Interns, 1972-1975 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Rhode Island, 1972-1975 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Right to Work Laws, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- South Carolina, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- South Dakota, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Teachers-AFT, NEA, AAUP and Others, 1973-1975 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Tennessee (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Tennessee-Memphis Govt. Wages, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Tennessee-Nashville Govt. Wages, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Texas, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Tobacco Workers International Union, AFL-CIO, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- United Steelworkers of America, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Utah, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Vermont, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Virginia, 1973-1975 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Washington, DC, 1973-1975 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- West Virginia, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- White Collar Wages, 1972-1975 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Wisconsin, 1973-1975 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Connecticut, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Indiana, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Maryland, 1973-1975 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Massachusetts, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Michigan, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- New Jersey, 1973-1975 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- New Jersey, Dept. of Health, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- New Jersey, Hospitals, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- New Jersey Hospitals, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- New Jersey Nursing Homes (Box 21, Folder 2)
- New York, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- New York City Hospitals, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- New York City Labor (Box 21, Folder 5)
- New York Health and Hospital Corp., 1975 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- New York Labor Law (Box 21, Folder 7)
- New York State Nursing Homes, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Ohio, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Organizing Material, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Organizing Material, 1970-1975 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Organizing Material-75 - Bob Muehlen Kamp, 1970-1975 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Osteopathic Hospital AOHA, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Pennsylvania II99C - Philadelphia, 1973-1975 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Pennsylvania 1199P - State College, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Public Employees Union, 1972-1975 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Wisconsin, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Cost of Living Council (Washington, DC) (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Blampied-Bradford 1199 Mass., 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Broad St. 1199C, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- California-75, 1967-1975 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- College Mental Health 1199 Mass., 1974 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Election Information - Connecticut, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Election Information, 1199E (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Election Information, II99P (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Election Information, New Jersey, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Election Information, New York, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Episcopal Hospital 1199C, 1972-1974 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Greater Baltimore 1199E, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Jewish Memorial 1199, Mass., 1973 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Einstein 1199C, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- 1199C, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Georgetown 1199, DC, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Hahnemann Hospital, 1199C, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Health Care Elections, General Information, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Illinois, 1968-1973 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Illinois-Iowa, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Indiana, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Inglis 1199C, 1969-1972 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Johns Hopkins, 1199E, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Lutheran Hospital of Maryland, 1199E, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Maryland General, 1199E, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Mass. 1199, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Mass. University Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Medical College of Pa. 1199C, 1972-1974 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Mercy Hospital 1199P, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Metropolitan Hospital 1199C, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Michigan, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Michigan, Dearborn, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Michigan, Detroit, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Michigan, Kalamazoo, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Michigan, Trenton, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Michigan, Wayne-74, 1972-1974 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Missouri, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- NLRB Activity Reports, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- National Union (Misc.), 1972-1974 (Box 23, Folder 38)
- National Union Monthly, Report Form, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 39)
- Negley House, 1199P, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 40)
- New York, Buffalo, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 41)
- New York, Elmira, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 42)
- Ohio, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 43)
- Orthodox Jewish Home,1199H, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 44)
- Park Community Hospital, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 45)
- Philadelphia Geriatric 1199C, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 46)
- Philadelphia Osteopathic Hospital, 1199C, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 47)
- Provident Hospital 1199E, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 48)
- Rogers Memorial 1199DC, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 49)
- Sinai of Baltimore 1199E, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 50)
- Temple University 1199C, 1973-1975 (Box 23, Folder 51)
- Thomas Jefferson 1199C, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 52)
- Unfair Labor Practices - RI, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 53)
- Utica-Rochester, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 54)
- West Virginia.-Kentucky, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 55)
- Wisconsin, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 56)
- AFL-CIO Public Relations, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Benefit Plan 1199, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Brownstein, Allen, Mass., 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Bureau of Labor Stat. NY, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Bureau of National Affairs, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Cases, Board Units, 1199, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Catholic Hospital Assn, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Connecticut 1199, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Convention, National Union, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Davis, Leon, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Health Care - Hospitals, 1972-1975 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Health Care Material, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Health Care - Nursing Homes, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Health Care - Quality, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Health Education and Welfare, 1973-1975 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Health Industry, 1968-1973 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Health Maintenance, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Health Manpower, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Health Planning Council, NJ, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Hospitals - Construction, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Hospital. Corporation of America, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Hospitals - Legislation, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Hospitals - Overview, 1973-1975 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Hospital Planning Councils, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Hospitals - Trustees, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- 1199C, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- 1199DC, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- 1199 General, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- 1199M, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- 1199P, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Illinois-Iowa, 1199, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Indiana, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Labor Studies Center, 1973-1975 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Maintenance, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Mass 1199, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- McKinsey and Co., Inc., NY (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Miller, Thomas W. Jr. DC (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous Congressmen and Senators (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous Organizing Leaflets, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Modern Health Care (Box 25, Folder 18)
- New Jersey, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- New Jersey - Congressmen and Senators, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- New York - Congressmen and Senators, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- New York Health Care, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Ohio, 1199, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Olson, Jesse, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Pension, 1199, 1970-1975 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- RN's, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Rhode Island, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Rochester, 1199, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Rochester, NY Hospitals, 1972-1975 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- St. Louis, Missouri, 1199, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Simons, Jesse, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Superintendent of Documents, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Textile Workers NLRB Testimony, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Weinstock, Harry, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- West Virginia, 1199, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 35)
- AFSCME, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- American Hospital Association, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- American Medical Association, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Blue-Cross-Blue Shield, General, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Charter Medical Corp., 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Connecticut Hospitals and Nursing Homes, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Contracts-Constitutions of 1199, 1972-1975 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Fact Finding, 1199 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- FMCS, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Health Care Costs, 1970-1975 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Labor Study Group (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Lackawanna, NY, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Lockport, NY, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Lost and Won Elections, 1970-1975 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Lutheran Hospital Assn., 1942-1944 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Malpractice Insurance, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Maryland Health Dept., 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Maryland Nursing Homes, 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Mediator-FMCS, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Medicare-Medicaid, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Medic enters of America, Inc., 1975 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Meeting 1199C, 1973-1975 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Meeting 1199E, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- Meeting 1199P, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- Mental Health Stats, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- Multinational, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- NLRB (Box 27, Folder 28)
- New England Labor, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 29)
- New York, 1972-1975 (Box 27, Folder 30)
- Pennsylvania, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- Syracuse, NY, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 32)
- Youngstown, Ohio SEIU-75, 1972-1975 (Box 27, Folder 33)
- Washington, DC (Box 27, Folder 34)
- Washington, DC - Government Wages (Box 27, Folder 35)
- Washington, Seattle, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 36)
- West Virginia-74, 1972-1974 (Box 27, Folder 37)
- Wisconsin, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 38)
- Wisconsin Economic Indicators, 1973-1975 (Box 27, Folder 39)
- Wisconsin Labor Law-71, 1965-1971 (Box 27, Folder 40)
- Wisconsin-Milwaukee Wages, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 41)
- Activities Report, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Albany Pharmacists Delegation, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Amended Constitution of 1199, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Annual Drug Membership Reports, 1968-1971 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Annual Statistical Reports, 1963-1970 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- APHA Newsletter, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Area Appeals and Grievances (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Area Delegate Assembly, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  Scope and Contents
  Sept. 1965.
- Area Director Grievance Reports, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Area Meeting Reports (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Area Membership Meetings, 1963-1965 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Areas - General (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Benefit Plan Statistics, 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Bronx Area -Hearing Appeals Board, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Civil Service - Benefit Pain - Dental & Eye Care Benefits, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Civil Service - Career & Salary Plan Resolution, 1964-1965 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Civil Certifications, 1973-1976 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Civil Service - Commission of NYC Rules (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Civil Service - Contract Negotiations, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Civil Service - Contracts, 1973-1976 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Civil Service - Directors of Pharmacy, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Civil Service - Health & Hospital Corp., 1973-1976 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Civil Service - Impasse Panel, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Civil Service - Minutes of Pharmacists -Membership Meeting, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Civil Service - Meeting Notices, 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Civil Service - Pay Plan Regulations, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Civil Service - Pharmacists - General, 1968-1970 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Civil Service - Pharmacists Grievances, 1970-1972 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Civil Service - Pharmacists Listing, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Civil Service - Pharmacists Negotiations, 1966-1973 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Civil Service - Pharmacists Negotiations, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Civil Service - Pharmacists Negotiations & Contracts (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Civil Service - Pharmacists Severance, Vacation, Back Pay, etc., 1967-1971 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Civil Service - Principal Pharmacists, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Civil Service - Tuition Reimbursement Form, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 18)
- Civil Service - Upgrading of Titles Requests, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 19)
- Civil Service - Wage Freeze, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 20)
- Clinical Labs Legislation, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Colleges of Pharmacy - Correspondence and Literature, 1962-1969 (Box 30, Folder 22)
- Decals, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Delegate Assembly Minutes and Meeting Notices, 1965-1973 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Delegate Attendance, 1967-1968 (Box 30, Folder 25)
- Delegate Attendance Reports, 1968-1974 (Box 30, Folder 26)
- Delegate Banquet Attendance, 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Delegate Newsletters, 1971-1974 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Delegate Tally Sheets, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Delegate Training Classes, 1963-1968 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Delegates: New and Dropped, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Director's Reports (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Drug Abuse Program, 1967-1970 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Drug Area Council - Area Delegate Assembly, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  Oct. 1963.
- Drug Division Organization (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Drug Industry Contract Advisory Committee, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Drug Plans: Re use of 1199 Stores, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Drug Staff Meetings, 1968-1972 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Election Committee Meetings, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Employee Organization Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Gatte, Philip Fund, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- General Membership Meeting Notices-74, 1964-1974 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Generic Drugs, I96I-69, 1961-1969 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Glotzer, George - Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Handbooks: CPA, Podiatry, Dentistry, Osteopathy, etc., 1957 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Impasse Panel Forms, 1968-1971 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Industry Petition to Wage Bond, Dec., 1971 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Kamenkowitz, P. - Correspondence-75, 1971-1975 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- King, Martin Luther Jr. - Memorial, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Legislation-68, 1967-1968 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Letters: Delinquent Delegates, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Melcher, Simon, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- National Health Insurance Committee, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- NYS Board of Pharmacy - Employee Nominations for Membership (Box 33, Folder 1)
- NYS Board of Pharmacy - Pharmacies Processed-76, 1970-1976 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- NYS Board of Pharmacy - Representation (Box 33, Folder 3)
- NYS Council of Hospital Pharmacists, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- NYS Legislative Program of the Liberal Party, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Organizational Material, 1969-1971 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Peace Committee, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Pharmacists - General, 1966-1969 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Pharmacy Legislation, 1961-1966 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Prepaid Prescription Plan, 1967-1968 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Prepaid Prescriptions, 1959-1966 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Professional Pharmacists Guild of Delaware Valley, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Promotion Campaigns, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Quarterly and Monthly Statistics, 1961-1967 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Report on Program of Labor Relations for NYC Employees (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Self-Insured Drug Plans in NYC, 1966-1967 (Box 34, Folder 2)